You're right.
أنت على حق.
The moment you can rely on a man
في اللحظة التي يمكنك الاعتماد فيها على الرجل
Is when sows are able to climb trees.
عندما تكون الخنازير قادرة على تسلق الأشجار.
How did you come up here?
كيف أتيت إلى هنا؟
Human and machine as one.
الإنسان والآلة في آن واحد.
Then you're not an individual.
ثم أنت لست فردا.
Go on.
تابع.
Who told you to get close to Little Sparrow?
من قال لك أن تقترب من العصفور الصغير؟
I'm the one
أنا واحد
speak for yourself.
تتحدث عن نفسك.
What's the purpose of your approaching her?
ما الهدف من اقترابك منها؟
What's your purpose?
ما هو غرضك؟
I really do.
أنا حقا.
Shameless!
وقح!
That's right.
صحيح.
You're so shameless.
أنت وقح جدا.
You left her alone in the restaurant.
لقد تركتها وحدها في المطعم.
I'm going back to her now.
سأعود إليها الآن.
Thank you for the call.
شكرا لك على المكالمة.
I'll pick her up now.
سأصطحبها الآن.
Wasn't it charged in the morning?
لم يتم شحنها في الصباح؟
Jinmu.
مشاعرنا.
Gold moth, here you go.
فراشة الذهب، هنا تذهب.
You're not a human then.
أنت لست إنسانا بعد ذلك.
Why is your heart beating so loud?
لماذا قلبك ينبض بصوت عال؟
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Hey!
يا!
Put me down!
انزلني!
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
It's because you ran so fast.
هذا لأنك ركضت بسرعة كبيرة.
Where's Xu Lai?
أين شو لاي؟
I recharged his car.
لقد قمت بإعادة شحن سيارته.
But I charged it with restraint.
لكنني اتهمته بضبط النفس.
How can you speak
كيف يمكنك التحدث
It's weird.
هذا غريب.
I'm Jin Mulai.
أنا الجني ابدأ.
Can you be a person?
هل يمكنك أن تكون شخصًا؟
You left my car battery,
لقد تركت بطارية سيارتي،
I came here by taxi.
جئت إلى هنا بسيارة أجرة.
Little sparrow.
العصفور الصغير.
Nice to see you again.
جميل ان اراك مرة اخرى.
Boss, get in the car.
أيها الرئيس، اصعد إلى السيارة.
I asked the professor to sign the contract.
طلبت من الأستاذ أن يوقع العقد.
Oh!
أوه!
Little sparrow.
العصفور الصغير.
We will meet soon.
سنلتقي قريبا.
I'll leave then.
سأغادر بعد ذلك.
Well
حسنًا
what is this?
ما هذا؟
Angela.
أنجيلا.
Lisa.
ليزا.
Bella,
بيلا،
jessica, this is your gift.
جيسيكا، هذه هديتك.
To fit in the trunk.
لتناسب في الجذع.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
Little Sparrow,
العصفور الصغير،
I can explain.
أستطيع أن أشرح.
Little sparrow.
العصفور الصغير.
I...
أنا...
Boss.
رئيس.
Are you possessive!
هل أنت متملك!
Think positively.
فكر بإيجابية.
Little girls will have a boyfriend sooner or later.
الفتيات الصغيرات سيكون لديهن صديق عاجلاً أم آجلاً.
I think you want to be fired.
أعتقد أنك تريد أن تطرد.
She is using a computer even when she's sleeping.
إنها تستخدم الكمبيوتر حتى أثناء نومها.
Grandpa asked me to find the secret of little sparrow
لقد طلب مني جدي أن أجد سر العصفور الصغير
Is inside this.
موجود داخل هذا.
Jin Mu Lai.
جين مو لاي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Speak out.
أفصح.
Are you trying to copy the idol drama model secretly?
هل تحاول نسخ نموذج الدراما المعبود سرا؟
And earn some money?
وكسب بعض المال؟
Right.
يمين.
I owe you a lot of money.
أنا مدين لك بالكثير من المال.
So I...
لذا أنا...
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
You
أنت
just stay here.
فقط ابقى هنا.
Don't let Xu Lai influence you.
لا تدع Xu Lai يؤثر عليك.
He is fickle in love no matter how rich he is.
فهو متقلب في الحب مهما كان غنيا.
Don't...
لا...
About money?
بشأن المال؟
Of course I do.
بالطبع افعل.
But I only care about the money you owe me.
لكني أهتم فقط بالمال الذي تدين به لي.
I'm going back to sleep.
أنا ذاهب إلى النوم.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
Don't come in my bedroom again.
لا تأتي في غرفة نومي مرة أخرى.
It is improper for men and women to be improperly intimate.
من غير المناسب أن يكون الرجل والمرأة حميميين بشكل غير لائق.
You are dismissed.
انت مطرود.
Little sparrow.
العصفور الصغير.
Xu Lai told me about everything.
أخبرني شو لاي عن كل شيء.
Are you really going to
هل أنت حقا ذاهب ل
with an unknown jerk?
مع رعشة مجهولة؟
How can you stop me?
كيف يمكنك أن توقفني؟
I know, Mom.
أنا أعلم يا أمي.
You're the president.
أنت الرئيس.
You have money.
انت تملك المال.
Keep the change.
احتفظ بالباقي.
Why are you pretending to have no money?
لماذا تتظاهر بعدم وجود المال؟
How could you?
كيف استطعت؟
About money?
بشأن المال؟
Of course I do.
بالطبع افعل.
Grandpa didn't send me to the Earth
جدي لم يرسلني إلى الأرض
to make money, right?
لكسب المال، أليس كذلك؟
Just go.
فقط اذهب.
Granny Hua.
الجدة هوا.
The business is good today.
العمل جيد اليوم.
I've earned a lot of money today.
لقد كسبت الكثير من المال اليوم.
Young man, do you have any money?
أيها الشاب، هل لديك أي أموال؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
No. You hurt my leg.
لا، لقد آذيت ساقي.
Sorry, grandma.
آسف يا جدتي.
I want to earn money.
أريد كسب المال.
If you want to earn money,
إذا كنت تريد كسب المال،
find it yourself.
تجدها بنفسك.
It's not easy for me to find it.
ليس من السهل بالنسبة لي العثور عليه.
How can it earn money?
كيف يمكن أن تكسب المال؟
Young man,
شاب،
this one
هذا
this one.
هذا.
Xiao Wu,
شياو وو,
hurry.
عجل.
Bring the sofa here.
أحضر الأريكة هنا.
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
Young man,
شاب،
he's still young.
انه لا يزال شابا.
She'll become
سوف تصبح
she'll be an expert in picking up trash.
ستكون خبيرة في جمع القمامة.
You're really something.
أنت حقا شيء.
Team up with me to pick up trash.
تعاون معي لجمع القمامة.
It's time to prove myself.
حان الوقت لإثبات نفسي.